1. [Leaderboards](https://aimlab.gg/leaderboards)
2. [Discovery](https://aimlab.gg/discovery)
3. [Articles](https://aimlab.gg/articles)
4. [Mouse Sensitivity](https://aimlab.gg/mouse-sensitivity-converter)

Log in

Privacy Policy
==============

Last Updated: 10/2/2023, 6:48 PM

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Last Updated: October 2, 2023

State Space Labs, Inc. (“**Statespace**,” “**we**,” “**us**” or “**our**”) provides the Aim Lab software and other training resources to allow our customers to improve their gaming and other skills. This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, process, and share your personal information, and to help you understand and exercise your privacy rights

Let’s get one thing clear: **Statespace has never, does not and will not make money from the sale of your personal information**. We run our business by building the best products and Services, not selling your info. In order to give you the best gaming experience, we may share your information with our partners to promote our own products and Services, as described below.

1\. SCOPE

2\. PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

3\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

4\. HOW WE DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION

5\. YOUR PRIVACY CHOICES AND RIGHTS

6\. SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

7\. INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS

8\. RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

9\. SUPPLEMENTAL NOTICE FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

10\. SUPPLEMENTAL NOTICE FOR VIRGINIA, COLORADO AND CONNECTICUT RESIDENTS

11\. SUPPLEMENTAL NOTICE FOR NEVADA RESIDENTS

12\. CHILDREN’S INFORMATION

13\. OTHER PROVISIONS

14\. CONTACT US

**SCOPE**

This Privacy Policy applies to personal information processed by us, including on our websites, software, mobile applications, and other online or offline offerings. To make this Privacy Policy easier to read, our websites and other offerings are collectively called “**Services.**”

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We collect personal information both from our user customers (“**Users**”), as well as from our expert coaches and content creators (“**Creators**”) who provide personalized online training (“**Coaching Services**”) as well as other. The categories of personal information we collect depend on how you interact with us, our Services, and the requirements of applicable law. We collect information that you provide to us, information we obtain automatically when you use our Services, and information from other sources such as third-party services and organizations, as described below.

**A. Information You Provide to Us Directly**

We may collect the following personal information that you provide to us.

* **Account Creation**
    
    . Depending on whether you are a User or Creator, we may collect the following information to set up your account (“
    
    **Account**
    
    ”)
    
    **:**
    
* **Users:** 
    
    we may collect your
    
    email address, public-facing username, and password. If you create an Account or connect an existing account using your login credentials from a third-party social media account such as Discord,
    
    Twitch, Apple,
    
    or Google, we’ll be able to access and collect your name and email address and other personal information as determined by your third-party social media account settings. If you choose to link your Account to an account you have with a third-party video game provider (such as your Riot account), we may import user data from your third-party game account and public APIs to display additional statistics in your Account profile page, and correlate that data on our own backend with other data you provide through our Services (as described below).
    
* **Creators (Coaches)**
    
    : We may collect your email address, name, signature, link to social channels, supported games, payment information, photo, links to your prior coaching or other game-related content, your desired coaching rate, and other information about your interests and expert qualifications. You will also have the option to share information about yourself via our Services with other Users.
    
* **Interactive Features**
    
    . We and other Users may collect personal information that you submit or make available through our interactive features (e.g., messaging and chat features, commenting functionalities, forums, blogs, and social media pages like our Discord channel). Any information you provide using the public sharing features of the Services (referred to herein as “
    
    **User Content**
    
    ”) will be considered “public,” unless otherwise required by applicable law, and is not subject to the privacy protections referenced herein. Please exercise caution before revealing any information that may identify you in the real world to other users.
    
* **Additional note regarding Coaching Services.**
    
     The Coaching Services may include additional activities, such as one-on-one training sessions, interactive seminars/classes, Video-On-Demand reviews of gameplay, Q&A sessions, personalized playlists, tasks or training regiments, or other similar services, as selected by the Creator. All of these Coaching Services may require both Creators and Users to provide additional personal information to us, which we will collect and store as part of your Account and use to determine whether the Coaching Services have been delivered as promised. 
    
* **Purchases**
    
    . We may collect personal information and details associated with your purchases (including your subscriptions), including payment information. Any payments made via our Services are processed by third-party payment processors. We do not directly collect or store any payment card information entered through our Services, but we may receive information associated with your payment card information (e.g., your billing details).
    
* **Your Communications with Us**
    
    . We may collect personal information, such as email address, phone number, or mailing address when you request information about our Services, register for our newsletter or loyalty program, request customer or technical support, apply for a job, or otherwise communicate with us.
    
* **Surveys**
    
    . We may contact you to participate in surveys. If you decide to participate, you may be asked to provide certain information which may include personal information.
    
* **Sweepstakes, Tournaments, or Contests**
    
    . We may collect personal information you provide for any sweepstakes, tournaments or contests that we offer. In some jurisdictions, we are required to publicly share information of sweepstakes and contest winners. In the event that you enter personal information on behalf of teammates in a tournament or contest, you represent and warrant that you have consent to do so.
    
* **Conferences, Trade Shows, and Other Events.**
    
     We may collect personal information from individuals when we attend conferences, trade shows, and other events. 
    
* **Business Development and Strategic Partnerships.**
    
     We may collect personal information from individuals and third parties to assess and pursue potential business opportunities. 
    
* **Job Applications.**
    
     We may post job openings and opportunities on our Services. If you reply to one of these postings by submitting your application, CV and/or cover letter to us, we will collect and use your information to assess your qualifications.

**B. Information Collected Automatically** 

We may collect personal information automatically when you use our Services:

* **Your Stats and Skill Level**
    
    . When you interact with our Services, such as our Aim Lab software, we collect detailed statistics about your play history, including your performance and scores in certain Aim Lab tasks. These scores are used to assess your strengths and weaknesses, as well as your skill level and rank which are visible to other Users as part of your public profile. Additionally, your scores on Aim Lab tasks are shared with other Users via our leaderboards, but you can make your presence on our leaderboard anonymous.
    
* **Automatic Data Collection**
    
    . We may collect certain information automatically when you use our Services, such as your Internet protocol (IP) address, user settings, MAC address, cookie identifiers, mobile carrier, mobile advertising and other unique identifiers, browser or device information, location information (including approximate location derived from IP address), and Internet service provider. We may also automatically collect information regarding your use of our Services, such as pages that you visit before, during and after using our Services, information about the links you click, the types of content you interact with, the frequency and duration of your activities, and other information about how you use our Services. 
    
* **Cookies, Pixel Tags/Web Beacons, and Other Technologies**
    
    . We, as well as third parties that provide content, advertising, or other functionality on our Services, may use cookies, pixel tags, local storage, and other technologies (“
    
    **Technologies**
    
    ”) to automatically collect information through your use of our Services. 
    
* **Cookies**
    
    . Cookies are small text files placed in device browsers that store preferences and facilitate and enhance your experience.
    
* **Pixel Tags/Web Beacons**
    
    . A pixel tag (also known as a web beacon) is a piece of code embedded in our Services that collects information about engagement on our Services. The use of a pixel tag allows us to record, for example, that a user has visited a particular web page or clicked on a particular advertisement. We may also include web beacons in e-mails to understand whether messages have been opened, acted on, or forwarded.

Our uses of these Technologies fall into the following general categories: 

* **Operationally Necessary**
    
    . This includes Technologies that allow you access to our Services, applications, and tools that are required to identify irregular website behavior, prevent fraudulent activity and improve security or that allow you to make use of our functionality;
    
* **Performance-Related**
    
    . We may use Technologies to assess the performance of our Services, including as part of our analytic practices to help us understand how individuals use our Services (
    
    _see Analytics below_
    
    ). For example, we may track your in-app activity, including recordings of your gameplay and other interactions with the Aim Lab software;
    
* **Functionality-Related**
    
    . We may use Technologies that allow us to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing or using our Services. This may include identifying you when you sign into our Services or keeping track of your specified preferences, interests, or past items viewed;
    
* **Advertising- or Targeting-Related**
    
    . We may use first party or third-party Technologies to deliver content, including ads relevant to your interests, on our Services or on third-party websites.

_See "_Your Privacy Choices and Rights" _below to understand your choices regarding these Technologies._

* **Analytics**
    
    . We may use Technologies and other third-party tools to process analytics information on our Services. Some of our analytics partners include:
    
* **Google Analytics**
    
    . We use analytics services provided by Google Inc. This allows us to process usage data to better understand how our website and web-related Services are used. This enables us to continually improve our website, making it relevant to your interests and needs. This may involve personal data, such as cookie and other device identifiers. The data collected by Google Analytics is usually transferred to a Google server in the USA and processed there. In addition, Google uses your data for its own purposes, e.g. for profiling or linking it to other data. For more information, please visit 

    . To learn more about how to opt-out of Google Analytics’ use of your information, please click 

    .
    
* **Segment**
    
    . For more information, including how to opt out, please visit Segment’s 

    .
    
* **Rudderstack**
    
    . For more information, including how to opt out, please visit Rudderstack’s

    . 
    
* **Sprig**
    
    . For more information, including how to opt out, please visit Sprig’s

    . 
    
* **New Relic**
    
    . For more information, including how to opt out, please visit New Relic’s 

    . 
    
* **Inspectlet**
    
    . For more information, including how to opt out, please visit Inspectlet’s

    and

    page
    
    .
    
* **Social Media Platforms.** 
    
    Our Services may contain
    
    social media buttons such as Discord, Instagram, Reddit, Twitter, or YouTube (that might include widgets such as the “share this” button or other interactive mini programs). These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Services, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Your interactions with these platforms are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**C. Information Collected from Other Sources**

We may obtain information about you from other sources, including through third-party services and organizations. For example, if you access our Services through a third-party application, such as an app store (like Steam), connect your Account with us to an external third-party gaming account such as your Steam, Xbox, PSN, and Battle.net account, or utilize a third-party login service or a social networking site, we may collect information about you from that third-party application or account that you have made available via your privacy settings. We allow interactions with third parties to make your experience better, but our Privacy Policy doesn’t and can’t apply to entities we don’t own, control, or instruct. We’re unable to guarantee that independent third parties adhere to the same practices as us, so please be sure to read their policies and terms before sharing info with them. In addition, we may collect information that other people provide about you when they use our Services, including information about you when they tag you.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

We use your information for a variety of business purposes, including to provide our Services, for administrative purposes, and to market our products and Services, as described below. 

**A. Provide Our Services**

We use your information to fulfil our contract with you and provide you with our Services, such as:

* Managing your information and Accounts;
    
* Providing access to certain areas, functionalities, and features of our Services;
    
* Answering requests for customer or technical support; 
    
* Communicating with you about your Account, activities on our Services, and policy changes;
    
* Processing your financial information and other payment methods for products or Services purchased;
    
* Processing applications if you apply for a job we post on our Services; and
    
* Allowing you to register for events.

**B. Administrative Purposes**

We use your information for various administrative purposes, such as:

* Pursuing our legitimate interests such as direct marketing, research and development (including marketing research), network and information security, and fraud prevention;
    
* Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity;
    
* Measuring interest and engagement in our Services; 
    
* Short-term, transient use, such as contextual customization of ads;
    
* Improving, upgrading or enhancing our Services; 
    
* Developing new products and Services;
    
* Ensuring internal quality control and safety;
    
* Authenticating and verifying individual identities, including requests to exercise your rights under this policy;
    
* Debugging to identify and repair errors with our Services;
    
* Auditing relating to interactions, transactions and other compliance activities;
    
* Sharing information with third parties as needed to provide the Services, such as the Coaching Services;
    
* Enforcing our agreements and policies; and
    
* Complying with our legal obligations.

**C. Marketing and Advertising our Products and Services**

We may use personal information to tailor and provide you with content and advertisements. We may provide you with these materials as permitted by applicable law. Some of the ways we market to you include email campaigns, and “interest-based” or “personalized advertising,” including through cross-device tracking. If you have any questions about our marketing practices or if you would like to opt out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes, you may contact us at any time as set forth in “Contact Us” below. 

**D. Other Purposes**

We also use your information for other purposes as requested by you or as permitted by applicable law.

* **Consent**
    
    . We may use personal information for other purposes that are clearly disclosed to you at the time you provide personal information or with your consent.
    
* **Automated Decision-Making**
    
    .
    
    We may engage in automated decision making, including profiling, such as to analyze your skill and identify areas of improvement. Statespace’s processing of your personal information will not result in a decision based solely on automated processing that significantly affects you unless such a decision is necessary as part of a contract we have with you, we have your consent, or we are permitted by law to engage in such automated decision making. If you have questions about our automated decision making, you may contact us as set forth in “Contact Us” below.
    
* **De-identified and Aggregated Information**
    
    . We may use personal information and other information about you to create de-identified and/or aggregated information, such as de-identified demographic information, information about the device from which you access our Services, or other analyses we create.
    
* **Share Content with Friends or Colleagues**
    
    . Our Services may offer various tools and functionalities. For example, we may allow you to provide information about your friends through our referral services. Our referral services may allow you to forward or share certain content with a friend or colleague, such as an email inviting your friend to use our Services. Please only share with us contact information of people with whom you have a relationship (e.g., relative, friend neighbor, or co-worker).

**HOW WE DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION**

We disclose your information to third parties for a variety of business purposes, including to provide our Services, to protect us or others, or in the event of a major business transaction such as a merger, sale, or asset transfer, as described below. 

**A. Disclosures to Provide our Services**

The categories of third parties with whom we may share your information are described below. 

* **Creators (for Coaching Services).** 
    
    If you participate in Coaching Services, your gameplay and other information will be accessible by your Creator coach.
    
* **Other Users.**
    
     As described above in “Personal Information We Collect,” our Services allow you to share your profile and/or gameplay statistics with other Users and publicly, including to those who do not use our Services. 
    
* **Service Providers**
    
    . We may share your personal information with our third-party service providers who use that information to help us provide our Services. This includes service providers that provide us with IT support, hosting, payment processing, customer service, and related services.
    
* **Business Partners**
    
    . We may share your personal information with business partners to provide you with a product or service you have requested. We may also share your personal information to business partners with whom we jointly offer products or services.
    
* **Advertising Partners**
    
    . We may share your personal information with third-party advertising partners. These third-party advertising partners may set Technologies and other tracking tools on our Services to collect information regarding your activities and your device (e.g., your IP address, cookie identifiers, page(s) visited, location, time of day). These advertising partners may use this information (and similar information collected from other services) for purposes of delivering personalized advertisements to you when you visit digital properties within their networks. This practice is commonly referred to as “interest-based advertising” or “personalized advertising.”
    
* **APIs/SDKs**
    
    . We may use third-party Application Program Interfaces (“
    
    **APIs**
    
    ”) and Software Development Kits (“
    
    **SDKs**
    
    ”) as part of the functionality of our Services. For more information about our use of APIs and SDKs, please contact us as set forth in “Contact Us”
    
    below.

**B. Disclosures to Protect Us or Others**

We may access, preserve, and disclose any information we store associated with you to external parties if we, in good faith, believe doing so is required or appropriate to: comply with law enforcement or national security requests and legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; protect your, our, or others’ rights, property, or safety; enforce our policies or contracts; collect amounts owed to us; or assist with an investigation or prosecution of suspected or actual illegal activity.

**C. Disclosure in the Event of Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers**

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, purchase or sale of assets, or transition of service to another provider, your information may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction, as permitted by law and/or contract.

**YOUR PRIVACY CHOICES AND RIGHTS**

**Statespace has never, does not and will not make money from the sale of your personal information**. We run our business by building the best products and Services, not selling your info. In order to give you the best gaming experience, we may share your information with our partners to promote our own products and Services, as described below.

**Your Privacy Choices**. The privacy choices you may have about your personal information are determined by applicable law and are described below. 

* **Email Communications**
    
    . If you receive an unwanted email from us, you can use the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email to opt out of receiving future emails. Note that you will continue to receive transaction-related emails regarding products or Services you have requested. We may also send you certain non-promotional communications regarding us and our Services, and you will not be able to opt out of those communications (e.g., communications regarding our Services or updates to our Terms or this Privacy Policy). 
    
* **Mobile Devices**
    
    . We may send you push notifications through our mobile application. You may opt out from receiving these push notifications by changing the settings on your mobile device. With your consent, we may also collect precise location-based information via our mobile application. You may opt out of this collection by changing the settings on your mobile device.
    
* **“Do Not Track**
    
    .
    
    **”**
    
     Do Not Track (“
    
    **DNT**
    
    ”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. A DNT technology standard has not been adopted to this day, therefore and we do not respond to or honor DNT signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.
    
* **Cookies and Interest-Based Advertising**
    
    . You may stop or restrict the placement of Technologies on your device or remove them by adjusting your preferences as your browser or device permits. However, if you adjust your preferences, our Services may not work properly. Please note that cookie-based opt-outs are not effective on mobile applications. However, you may opt-out of personalized advertisements on some mobile applications by following the instructions for 

    , 

     and 

    .

The online advertising industry also provides websites from which you may opt out of receiving targeted ads from data partners and other advertising partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. You can access these and learn more about targeted advertising and consumer choice and privacy by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), [the Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), [the European Digital Advertising Alliance](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/), and [the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada](https://youradchoices.ca/choices/). 

Please note you must separately opt out in each browser and on each device.

**Your Privacy Rights**. In accordance with applicable law, you may have the right to:

* **Access Personal Information**
    
    about you, including: (i) confirming whether we are processing your personal information; (ii) obtaining access to or a copy of your personal information;
    
* **Request Correction**
    
    of your personal information where it is inaccurate, incomplete or outdated. In some cases, we may provide self-service tools that enable you to update your personal information;
    
* **Request Deletion, Anonymization or Blocking**
    
    of your personal information when processing is based on your consent or when processing is unnecessary, excessive or noncompliant;
    
* **Request Restriction of or Object to**
    
    our processing of your personal information when processing is noncompliant;
    
* **Withdraw your Consent**
    
    to our processing of your personal information. If you refrain from providing personal information or withdraw your consent to processing, some features of our Service may not be available;
    
* **Request data portability and receive an electronic copy of personal information that you have provided to us;**
    
* **Be informed**
    
    about third parties with which your personal information has been shared; and 
    
* **Request the review of decisions taken exclusively based on automated processing**
    
    if these decisions could affect your data subject rights;

If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us as set forth in “Contact Us” below. We will process such requests in accordance with applicable laws.

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, no system is 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us. We have taken appropriate safeguards to require that your personal information will remain protected and require our third-party service providers and partners to have appropriate safeguards as well. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we do not accept liability for unauthorized disclosure.

By using our Services or providing personal information to us, you agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of our Services. If we learn of a security system’s breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically by posting a notice on our Services, by mail or by sending an email to you.

**INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS** 

All information processed by us may be transferred, processed, and stored anywhere in the world, including, but not limited to, the United States or other countries, which may have data protection laws that are different from the laws where you live. We endeavor to safeguard your information consistent with the requirements of applicable laws.

If we transfer personal information to countries outside the European Economic Area, we will put in place appropriate safeguards to ensure that this transfer complies with the applicable laws and regulations. For more information about these safeguards, please contact us as set forth below.

**RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION** 

We store the personal information we collect as described in this Privacy Policy for as long as you use our Services or as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected, provide our Services, resolve disputes, establish legal defenses, conduct audits, pursue legitimate business purposes, enforce our agreements, and comply with applicable laws.  

**SUPPLEMENTAL NOTICES FOR RESIDENTS OF CALIFORNIA, NEVADA, COLORADO, CONNECTICUT, VIRGINIA AND UTAH**

**SUPPLEMENTAL NOTICE FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**

This Supplemental California Privacy Notice only applies to our processing of personal information that is subject to the California Consumer Privacy Act (“**CCPA**”). The CCPA provides California residents with the right to know what categories of personal information Statespace has collected about them and whether Statespace disclosed that personal information for a business purpose (e.g., to a service provider) in the preceding 12 months. California residents can find this information below:

**Category of Personal Information Collected by Statespace**

**Category of Third Parties Information is Disclosed to for a Business Purpose**

**Identifiers**

A real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, Account name, or other similar identifiers. 

* Advertising networks
    
* Data analytics providers
    
* Service providers
    
* Other Users/Public (username only)

**Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e))**

A name, signature, physical characteristics or description, address, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information. 

* Data analytics providers
    
* Service providers

**Commercial information**

Records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.

* Data analytics providers
    
* Service providers
    
* Advertising networks

**Biometric information**

Physiological, biological, or behavioral characteristics, keystroke patterns or rhythms.

* Data analytics providers
    
* Service providers
    
* Other Users/Public (performance metrics only)

**Internet or other electronic network activity**

Browsing history, search history, information on a consumer's interaction with an internet website, application, or advertisement.

* Data analytics providers
    
* Service providers
    
* Advertising networks

**Sensory data**

Audio, electronic, visual, or similar information.

* Data analytics providers
    
* Service providers
    
* Other Users/Public (performance metrics only)

**Inferences drawn from other personal information to create a profile about a consumer**

Profile reflecting a consumer's preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.

* Data analytics providers
    
* Service providers
    
* Other Users/Public (performance metrics only)
    
* Advertising networks

The categories of sources from which we collect personal information and our business and commercial purposes for using personal information are set forth in “Personal Information We Collect” and “How We Use Your Personal Information” above, respectively. 

**“Sales” of Personal Information under the CCPA**

Statespace does not “sell” personal information, nor do we have actual knowledge of any “sale” of personal information of minors under 16 years of age, as the term “sale” is commonly understood. That said, we do share information with third-party advertisers for the purpose of promoting our Services. To the extent that such sharing is considered a “sale” under the CCPA, you may opt-out of having your information shared by disabling third-party cookies on your device, or by contacting us as set forth in “Contact Us” below.

**Additional Privacy Rights for California Residents**

**Non-Discrimination.** California residents have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us for the exercise of their rights conferred by the CCPA.

**Authorized Agent.** Only you, or someone legally authorized to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child. To designate an authorized agent, please contact us as set forth in “Contact Us” below and provide written authorization signed by you and your designated agent.

**Verification**. To protect your privacy, we will take steps the following steps to verify your identity before fulfilling your request. When you make a request, we will ask you to provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative, which may include asking you to answer questions regarding your Account and use of our Services.

If you are a California resident and would like to exercise any of your rights under the CCPA, please contact us as set forth in “Contact Us” below. We will process such requests in accordance with applicable laws. 

**Refer-a-Friend and Similar Incentive Programs.** As described above in **How We Use Your Personal Information** (“Share Content with Friends or Colleagues”), we may offer referral programs or other incentivized data collection programs. For example, we may offer incentives to you such as discounts or promotional items or credit in connection with these programs, wherein you provide your personal information in exchange for a reward, or provide personal information regarding your friends or colleagues (such as their email address) and receive rewards when they sign up to use our Services. (The referred party may also receive rewards for signing up via your referral.) These programs are entirely voluntary and allow us to grow our business and provide additional benefits to you. The value of your data to us depends on how you ultimately use our Services, whereas the value of the referred party’s data to us depends on whether the referred party ultimately becomes a User and/or Creator and uses our Services. Said value will be reflected in the incentive offered in connection with each program.

**Accessibility**. This Privacy Policy uses industry-standard technologies and was developed in line with the World Wide Web Consortium’s Web Content Accessibility Guidelines, version 2.1**.** If you wish to print this policy, please do so from your web browser or by saving the page as a PDF.

**Right for minors to remove posted content.** Where required by law, California residents under the age of 18 may request to have their posted content or information removed from the publicly-viewable portions of the Services by contacting us directly as set forth in “Contact Us” below.

**SUPPLEMENTAL NOTICE FOR VIRGINIA, COLORADO AND CONNECTICUT RESIDENTS**

 The Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act (“**VCDPA**”), the Colorado Privacy Act (“**CPA**”) and the Connecticut Data Privacy Act (“**CTDPA**”) provide residents of Virginia, Colorado and Connecticut with specific rights regarding their personal information. This section describes the rights of consumers who are residents of Virginia, Colorado and Connecticut and explains how to exercise those rights.

**Access to Specific Information and Data Portability Rights.** You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information. Before we disclose information to you, we will ask you for information to verify your identity. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will disclose to you whether we process your personal information and provide you with access to your personal information. We will provide a copy of personal information we have obtained about you in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format. Please note that we may not disclose the information you have requested if we are unable to verify your identity. In addition, we may not disclose certain information that is covered by one or more exemptions, as outlined in the VCDPA, CPA and CTDPA.

**Deletion Request Rights.** You have the right to request that we delete personal information that we collected and retained. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies. If we deny your deletion request, we will inform you and explain the basis for our denial.

**Correction Request Rights.**You have the right to request that we correct inaccuracies in your personal information, taking into account the nature of the personal information and the purposes of the processing. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will correct your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies. If we deny your correction request, we will inform you and explain the basis for our denial.

**Appeals.** If we deny your request, you have the right to appeal our decision. We will respond to appeals from Virginia and Connecticut residents within 60 days. We will respond to appeals from Colorado residents within 45 days.

**How to Exercise Your Virginia, Colorado or Connecticut Privacy Rights.**To exercise any of the rights described above, please contact us directly as set forth in “Contact Us” below. You must describe your request with sufficient detail to allow us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

As noted earlier in this Privacy Policy, we respond only to requests that are verifiable consumer requests. Therefore, when you submit a request to us, we will seek to verify your identity by asking you to provide us with information that enables us to identify you, such as your email address. We also may use a third-party verification provider to verify your identity. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you. Making a request does not require you to create an account with us. We will only use personal information provided in a request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.

**SUPPLEMENTAL NOTICE FOR NEVADA RESIDENTS**

If you are a resident of Nevada, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of certain Personal Information to third parties who intend to license or sell that Personal Information. You can exercise this right by contacting us as set forth below with the subject line “Nevada Do Not Sell Request” and providing us with your name and the email address associated with your Account. Please note that we do not currently sell your Personal Information as sales are defined in Nevada Revised Statutes Chapter 603A. If you have any questions, please contact us as set forth below.

**CHILDREN’S INFORMATION**

The Services are not directed to children under 13 (or other age as required by local law), and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children.

If you are a parent or guardian and believe your child has uploaded personal information to our site without your consent, you may contact us as described in “Contact Us” below. If we become aware that a child has provided us with personal information in violation of applicable law, we will delete any personal information we have collected, unless we have a legal obligation to keep it, and terminate the child’s Account if applicable.

**OTHER PROVISIONS**

**Third-Party Websites/Applications.** The Services may contain links to other websites/applications and other websites/applications may reference or link to our Services. These third-party services are not controlled by us. We encourage our users to read the privacy policies of each website and application with which they interact. We do not endorse, screen or approve, and are not responsible for, the privacy practices or content of such other websites or applications. Providing personal information to third-party websites or applications is at your own risk. 

**Supervisory Authority**. If you are located in the European Economic Area, Switzerland, the United Kingdom or Brazil, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you believe our processing of your personal information violates applicable law.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time in our sole discretion. If there are any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you as required by applicable law. You understand and agree that you will be deemed to have accepted the updated Privacy Policy if you continue to use our Services after the new Privacy Policy takes effect.

**CONTACT US** 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, or to exercise your rights as detailed in this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

State Space Labs, Inc.

ATTN: Privacy

7461 South Avenue, Boardman, OH 44512

help@statespacelabs.com 

(347) 903-8016

1. [Privacy Policy](https://aimlab.gg/privacy-policy)
2. [Terms of Service](https://aimlab.gg/terms-of-service)
3. [Merch](https://www.maxgaming.com/en/asus-rog-aimlab)
4. [Join our Team!](https://jobs.lever.co/statespacelabs)
5. [Help Center](https://support.aimlabs.com/hc/en-us)

##### Join our

Aimlabs, Aimlabs logos, and other Aimlabs trademarks are trademarks or registered trademarks of State Space Labs, Inc. or its affiliates in the U.S. and elsewhere. Other names or brands are trademarks of their respective owners.

All Rights Reserved 2023 © State Space Labs, Inc.
